{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Wood \u0026 Composite Roof Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/40404/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40404,"taskName":"Wood Shake or Composite Roofing - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Wood Shake or Composite Roofing","xmTaskDescriptor":"Wood \u0026 Composite Roof Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":197,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"national local roofs exterior build","textMessagingName":"Inst Wood Shake Roof","rolloverLongDesc":"Made from overlapping wood shingles called shakes. Mostly rot resistant woods like cedar or redwood are used. This category is for when it is probable that repairs won't be sufficient \u0026 that total replacement is likely to be necessary.","rolloverShortDesc":"Usually made of cedar or redwood.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Wood Shake or Composite Roofing.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Composite or Wood Roof Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":65,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Wood Shake Roofing Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Wood Shake or Composite Roofing - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Wood Shake Roofing Project","urlName":"Wood-Shake-or-Composite-Roofing-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Composite or Wood Roof Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"national,local,roofs,exterior,build,Shake,License,exchange,Roofers,wood,roof,roofing,Composite,prescreened,,designs,wanted,conctractors,,rooofing,siding,roofers.com,replacement,bids,prosource","emcCategoryOid":-12061,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":698,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40404/":{"taskOID":40404,"originalTaskOID":40404,"setID":698,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6869,"questionDisplayText":"What is the nature of this project?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":9813,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely replace roof","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9814,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install roof on new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install roof on new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9815,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing roof","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5254,"questionDisplayText":"Wood Roofing Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of wood roofing do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7056,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood Shingles","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shingles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7053,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood Shakes","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shakes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7057,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood Shingles-Fire Resistant","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shingles-Fire Resistant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7054,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood Shakes-Fire Resistant","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shakes-Fire Resistant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5568,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which special features would you like for your roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5354,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ridge vent","answerDisplayText":"Ridge vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Snow guards or brackets","answerDisplayText":"Snow guards or brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2893,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters and downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Gutters and downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Turbine vents","answerDisplayText":"Turbine vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5769,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Skylight/Solar tube","answerDisplayText":"Skylight/Solar tube","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat tape","answerDisplayText":"Heat tape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6857,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water diverters","answerDisplayText":"Water diverters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6872,"questionDisplayText":"Stories in House","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6871,"questionDisplayText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6869,"questionDisplayText":"What is the nature of this project?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":9813,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely replace roof","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9814,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install roof on new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install roof on new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9815,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing roof","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9813,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely replace roof","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9814,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install roof on new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install roof on new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9815,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing roof","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5254,"questionDisplayText":"Wood Roofing Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of wood roofing do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7056,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood Shingles","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shingles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7053,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood Shakes","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shakes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7057,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood Shingles-Fire Resistant","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shingles-Fire Resistant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7054,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood Shakes-Fire Resistant","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shakes-Fire Resistant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7056,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood Shingles","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shingles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7053,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood Shakes","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shakes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7057,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood Shingles-Fire Resistant","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shingles-Fire Resistant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7054,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood Shakes-Fire Resistant","answerDisplayText":"Wood Shakes-Fire Resistant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5568,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which special features would you like for your roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5354,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ridge vent","answerDisplayText":"Ridge vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Snow guards or brackets","answerDisplayText":"Snow guards or brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2893,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters and downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Gutters and downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Turbine vents","answerDisplayText":"Turbine vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5769,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Skylight/Solar tube","answerDisplayText":"Skylight/Solar tube","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat tape","answerDisplayText":"Heat tape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6857,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water diverters","answerDisplayText":"Water diverters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5354,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ridge vent","answerDisplayText":"Ridge vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Snow guards or brackets","answerDisplayText":"Snow guards or brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2893,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters and downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Gutters and downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Turbine vents","answerDisplayText":"Turbine vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5769,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Skylight/Solar tube","answerDisplayText":"Skylight/Solar tube","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat tape","answerDisplayText":"Heat tape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6857,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water diverters","answerDisplayText":"Water diverters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6872,"questionDisplayText":"Stories in House","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6871,"questionDisplayText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564376525018pwspr013F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}